LBAW

	⁃	US01 - As a User, I want to view the products list ordered by the most liked to the least one, so that I see the products available. ✅ -> Pedro
	⁃	US02 - As a User, I want to review product details, so that I can read product specs. ❌
	⁃	US03 - As a User, I want to search products by name, so that I can find it quickly. ✅ -> Balazeiro
	⁃	US04 - As a User, I want to browse product categories, so that I can list every product with the same category. ✅ -> Rúben
	⁃	US05 - As a User, I want to view product reviews, so that I can read the opinions from the other users. ✅ -> Pedro



	⁃	US06 - As an Authenticated User, I want to add a product to shopping cart, so that I can buy the product later. ✅ -> Rúben
	⁃	US07 - As an Authenticated User, I want to manage shopping cart, so that I can manage the card items. ✅ -> Rúben
	⁃	US08 - As an Authenticated User, I want to checkout, so that my account is protected. ✅ -> Pedro
	⁃	US09 - As an Authenticated User, I want to buy the added products, so that I can conclude my purchase. ✅ -> Rúben
	⁃	US10 - As an authenticated User, I want to add a product to my Wishlist, so that I can save it for later. ✅ -> Rúben
	⁃	US11 - As an Authenticated User, I want to manage Wishlist, so that I can manage the items. ✅ -> Rúben
	⁃	US12 - As an Authenticated User, I want to manage my reviews, so that I can add/remove/edit them. ✅ -> Pedro
	⁃	US13 - As an Authenticated User, I want to delete my account, so that I don’t have an account in the site. ✅ -> Pedro
	⁃	US14 - As an Authenticated User, I want to edit my profile so that the system can have my updated personal information. ✅ -> Balazeiro



	⁃	US15 - As an Unauthenticated User, I want to sign in, so that I can access my profile. ✅ -> Balazeiro
	⁃	US16 - As an Unauthenticated User, I want to sign up, so that I can create my profile. ✅ -> Pedro



	⁃	US17 - As a Buyer, I want to manage order status, so that I can control the order’s flow. ✅ -> ?
	⁃	US18 - As a Buyer, I want to checkout, so that I can close my account. ✅ -> Pedro
	⁃	US19 - As a Buyer, I want to track my order, so that I can know when the order will arrive. ✅ -> Pedro



	⁃	US20 - As an Administrator, I want to manage order status, so that I can control the order’s flow. ✅ -> Balazeiro
	⁃	US21 - As an Administrator, I want to checkout, so that I can close my account. ✅ -> Pedro
	⁃	US22 - As an Administrator, I want to add a product, so that the user can buy it. ✅ -> Balazeiro
	⁃	US23 - As an Administrator, I want to manage product information, so that the users can get an updated version. ✅ -> Rúben
	⁃	US24 - As an Administrator, I want to manage the product stock, so that I can control the quantity of a certain product. ✅ -> Balazeiro
	⁃	US25 - As an Administrator, I want to manage product categories, so that I can change the categories list. ❌
	⁃	US26 - As an Administrator, I want to view users’ purchase history, so that I can add to users’ main page related content. ✅ -> Rúben
	⁃	US27 - As an Administrator, I want to response to reviews, so that I can clarify the users. ❌
	⁃	US28 - As an Administrator, I want to manage (add, edit or delete) FAQ, so that the users can have updated information. ✅ -> Pedro
